Benjamin Vaughan Papers 1746-1900 Mss.B.V46p
American Philosophical Society
- Series II. General Correspondence, 1746-1952; 6.5 linear feet (Box 2-27)
  - Als to Vaughan, Sarah Manning, 1796 March 7; 4 p.; Lansdowne, William Petty, Marquis of, 1737-1805
  - ALS to Samuel Vaughan and Son, 1796 April 9, 14; 3 p.; Spooner, Andrew,
  - ALS to Vaughan, Sarah Manning, 1796 April 19; 4 p.; Lansdowne, William Petty, Marquis of, 1737-1805
  - ALS to Vaughan, Samuel, 1762-, 1796 April 28; 3 p.; Vaughan, Sarah Manning
  - Als to [?], 1796 May 16; 2 p.; J.J
    In French.
  - ALcy to Whom it May concern, 1796 May 20; 1 p.; Monroe, James, 1758-1831
  - ALS Cy to Whom it may concern, [1796 may 21]; 1 p.; Paine, Thomas,
    Regarding John Martin.
  - ALS to Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839, 1796 June 5, 17; 3 p.; Spooner, Andrew,
  - ADS, Directoire Executif, [1796 June 12]; 1 p.; Republique Francaise
  - ALS to Mrs Vaughan, 1796 June 13; 2 p.; Toulmin, J
  - ALS to Vaughan, Sarah Manning, 1796 June 26; 5 p.; Merrick, Rebecca Vaughan
  - ALS to, 1796 July 6; 2 p.; Lister, William
  - ALS to Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839, 1796 August 5; 2 p.; Vaughan, Samuel, Sr., 1720-1802
  - ALS to Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839 and Spooner, Andrew, 1796 August 30; 2 p.; Taillasson, [?]
  - ALS to Vaughan, Sarah Manning, 1796 September 11; 3 p.; Lansdowne, William Petty, Marquis of, 1737-1805
  - Als to Vaughan, Sarah Manning, 1796 October 6; 4 p.; Vaughan, Sarah Hallowell
  - Als to Vaughan, Sarah Manning, 1796 October 14; 3 p.; Vaughan, Sarah Hallowell
  - Als to Vaughan, William, 1752-1850, 1796 November 1; 3 p.; Priestley, Joseph, 1733-1804
    Priestley's wife died.
  - Als to Greenleaf, James, 1796 November 5; 1 p.; Vaughan, John, 1756-1841
    Purchased originally with Abbott-Vaughan. Genealogy. Oct. 1953.
  - AM, Account of the different bays at Tobago, [1796 November 8]; 2 p.
  - Als to Vaughan, Samuel and Son, 1796 December 7; 1 p.; Spooner, Andrew,
  - Am, Epitaph for Harriet Vaughan, 1796 December 15; 1 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - Als to [Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835], [ca. 1796]; 1 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Sarah Manning, 1797 February 6; 2 p.; Vaughan, Samuel, Sr., 1720-1802
  - Als to Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839, 1797 March 4; 4 p.; Vaughan, Samuel, Sr., 1720-1802
    Concerning an account.
  - Als to Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839, 1797 March 15; 2 p.; Vaughan, Samuel, Sr., 1720-1802
  - ALS to Vaughan and Spooner, 1797 March 24; 1 p.; Cordes Rendtorff and Cordes
    Account of the Market in Hamburgh.
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1797 April 14; 2 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
    Resignation of trusteeship.
  - Ads, Receipt to Martin, John, 1797 April 21; 1 p.; [Seurd,] William Cappinger
  - ALS to Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839, 1797 July 1; 3 p.; Vaughan, Samuel, Sr., 1720-1802
    Concerning the sale of goods.
  - Als to Vaughan, Samuel and Son, 1797 July 15; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
    Regarding the sale of cargo.
  - Als to Vaughan, Samuel and Son, 1797 August 2; 2 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
    Housed with 1797 July 15.
  - ALS to Messrs. H. and L. Johnson, 1797 July 12; 1 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
    Regarding bill of exchange.
  - ALS to Vaughan, John, 1756-1841, 1797 July 14; 1 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, Samuel and Son, 1797 September 2; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, William, 1752-1850, 1797 September 2; 1 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
    Regarding accounts.
  - ALS to Vaughan, Samuel and son, 1797 September 2; 1 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Dexter, Dr, 1797 August 4; 1 p.; Gore, C
  - ALS to Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839, 1797 August 5; 1 p.; Spooner, Andrew,
    Regarding the sale of Cargo.
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1797 August 31; 1 p.; Jay, John
    Vaughan has arrived in America.
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1797 September 24; 3 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
    Description of Vaughan's house.
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1797 September 27; 1 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - AL to Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839, 1797 September; 4 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
    Discusses changes made to the house.
  - ALS to Vaughan, Sarah Manning, 1797 October 2; 4 p.; Vaughan, Rebecca Vaughan
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1797 October 3; 2 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ADS, Account with Andrew Spooner and Charles Vaughan, 1797 October 4; 13 p.; Vaughan, Samuel, Sr., 1720-1802
  - ALS to Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839, 1797 October 4; 1 p.; Vaughan, Samuel, Sr., 1720-1802
  - ALS to Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839, 1797 October 5; 3 p.; Vaughan, Sarah Hallowell
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1797 October 9; 1 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS toVaughan, Charles, 1759-1839, 1797 October 10; 2 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
    Regarding a bill.
  - ALS toVaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1797 October 15; 3 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS toVaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1797 October 18; 3 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS toVaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1797 October 24; 3 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS toVaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1797 November 1; 2 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS toVaughan, Charles, 1759-1839, 1797 November 1, 3; 7 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
    Issues concerning his house.
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1797 November 4; 3 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1797 November 5; 2 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1797 November 8; 2 p.; Vaughan, Sarah Hallowell
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1797 November 8; 3 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1797 November 10; 2 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1797 November 11; 5 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1797 November 14; 3 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1797 November 16; 1 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1797 November 19; 2 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1797 November 26; 1 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1797 November 26; 3 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
    Issues regarding the family house.
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1797 December 5; 3 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1797 December 13; 1 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1797 December 16; 2 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1797 December 24; 1 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1797 December 27; 3 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1797 December 30; 3 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ADS, Bill of mortality, [1797?]; 1 p.; Austin, Rev
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1798 January 5; 3 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1798 January 6; 3 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1798 January 10; 1 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1798 January 16; 3 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - AMS, An account of the method of preparing wood-land for cultivation, 1798 January 24; 8 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - Als to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1798 January 24; 1 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - Als to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1798 January 28; 2 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - Als to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1798 February 7; 4 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - Als to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1798 February 14; 1 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - Als to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1798 February 28; 3 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS Cy to Lansdowne, William Petty, Marquis of, 1737-1805, 1798 February; 4 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
    Very good description of Benjamin Vaughan's house and the well being of his family.
  - ALS to Vaughan, Sarah Manning, 1798 March 1; 3 p.; Merrick, John, 1766-1861
    Rebecca Vaughan is getting married.
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1798 March 7; 2 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
    concerning family estate in Jamaica.
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1798 March 18; 3 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Rebecca, [1798] March 21; 3 p.; Gee, J. P
    Congratulations on her marriage.
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1798 March 25; 3 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1798 April 1; 1 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1798 April 1; 1 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1798 April 4; 3 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1798 April 5; 3 p.; Merrick, John, 1766-1861
    Vaughan's sister Rebecca in marrying John Merrick.
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1798 April 8; 3 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1798 April 9; 1 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ADS, Register of the wedding of John Merrick and Rebecca Vaughan, 1798 April 10; 1 p.
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1798 April 11; 2 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1798 April 14; 3 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839, 1798 April 18; 3 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
    Regarding their accounts.
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1798 April 19; 3 p.; Priestley, Joseph, 1733-1804
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1798 May 6; 2 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1798 May 7; 1 p.; Snow, Gideon,
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1798 May 17; 2 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1798 May 18; 1 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1798 May 28; 1 p.; Snow, Gideon,
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1798 May 28, 30; 4 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS Cy to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1798 June 1; 2 p.; Eberling, Christoph Daniel,
    Regarding a book on America/
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1798 June 3; 4 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
    Regarding "expenses at home" and the sale of land.
  - ALS to Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839, 1798 June 6; 3 p.; Vaughan, Samuel, Sr., 1720-1802
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1798 June 12; 3 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1798 June 12; 2 p.; Vaughan, Sarah Hallowell
  - ALS to Merrick, Rebecca Vaughan, 1798 June 20; 1 p.; Bird, Robert
  - ALS to Vaughan, Sarah Manning, 1798 June 20; 4 p.; Collins, Harriet
    Harriet Vaughan is not well.
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1798 June 21; 3 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1798 June 24; 3 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Grand, Jean Luc le, 1798 July 3; 4 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - Als to Mrs. Sarah Vaughan, 1798 July 14; 3 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
    Regarding her accounts.
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1798 July 26; 18 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
    Concerning family property.
  - ALS to Vaughan, Sarah Manning, 1798 July 28; 3 p.; Griffin, Lucy,
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1798 July 30; 1 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Sarah Manning, 1798 August 2; 2 p.; Collins, Harriet
  - ALS to Brassy, Nathaniel and Heywood, Samuel, 1798 August 4; 1 p.; Manning, William, 1767-1849
    regarding the estate of Sarah Manning Vaughan's father.
  - Als to Vaughan, William, 1752-1850, 1798 August 7; 1 p.; Manning, William, 1767-1849
    Housed with letter, 1798 August 4.
  - Als to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1798 August 8; 1 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - Als to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1798 August 10; 1 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
    Regarding land.
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1798 August 11; 3 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Collins, John, 1798 August 11; 3 p.; Vaughan, Sarah Manning
    Harriet Vaughan is still ill.
  - AL to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1798 August 14; 1 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALs to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1798 August 19; 2 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALs to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1798 August 20; 2 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Samuel, 1720-1802 and Son, 1798 August 29; 2 p.; Spooner, Andrew,
  - ADS, Statement of, 1798 August 31; 2 p.; Vaughan, John, 1756-1841
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1798 September 1; 2 p.
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1798 September 1; 1 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1798 September 4; 4 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
    Includes copy.
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1798 September 15; 1 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1798 September 16; 2 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1798 September 19; 3 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
    Received a perscription for Harriet Vaughan.
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1798 September 21; 2 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839, 1798 September 22; 4 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1798 September 22; 3 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1798 September 22; 4 p.; Vaughan, Sarah Hallowell
    Samuel Vaughan is ill.
  - ALS to "dear brother", 1798 September 25; 3 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, Sarah Manning, 1798 September 29; 3 p.; Collins, John
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1798 September 29; 3 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Sarah Manning, 1798 September 30; 3 p.; Boinville, H. de,
  - ALS to Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839, 1798 October 1; 1 p.; Merrick, John, 1766-1861
  - AL to Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839, 1798 October 2; 4 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
    Request that Charles not show his correspondence to anyone.
  - ALS to Drummer, Nathaniel; Captain Randall; and Captain Grant, 1798 October 4; 6 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1798 October 7; 4 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1798 October 13; 2 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1798 October 25; 3 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1798 November 4; 3 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1798 November 5; 4 p.; Lansdowne, William Petty, Marquis of, 1737-1805
  - ALS to Mitchill, Samuel Lathan, 1798 November 10; 4 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Mitchill, Samuel Lathan, 1798 November 14; 3 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - Als to Vaughan, Samuel, 1720-1802, 1798 November 20; 8 p.; Vaughan, Samuel, 1762-1827
  - Als to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1798 November 24; 4 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1798 December 1; 5 p.; Collins, John
  - Als to Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839, 1798 December 6; 2 p.; Vaughan, Sarah Manning
    Harriet Vaughan is declining in health.
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1798 December 17; 2 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Messers. Taylor and Lees, 1798 December 22; 3 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1798 December 24; 4 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
    Regarding family land.
  - ALS to Messrs. Manning, Anderson, and Bosanquet, 1798 December 28; 3 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - AL to Vaughan, Mrs. Charles, 1798 December 28; 3 p.; Vaughan, Sarah Manning
    Harriet Vaughan died.
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1798 December 30; 3 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Sarah Manning, [1798]; 3 p.; Collins, Harriet
  - ALS to Merrick, Rebecca Vaughan, [1798]; 2 p.; J.D
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1799 January 2; 3 p.; Vuaghan, William, 1752-1850
    4 Copies
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1799 January 5; 1 p.; Nathan Jones
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1799 January 13; 3 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
    Regarding family accounts.
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1799 January 18; 4 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1799 January 19; 2 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Sarah Manning, 1799 January 28; 1 p.; Manning, William, 1767-1849
    Regarding a Will.
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1799 January 30; 1 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1799 January 30; 1 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - AL to Vaughan, William, 1752-1850, 1799 February 7, December 22; 2 p.; Vaughan, Samuel, Sr., 1720-1802
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1799 February 13; 2 p.; Snow, Gideon,
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1799 February 23; 2 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Sarah Manning, 1799 February 27; 2 p.; Savage, Sarah
    Regarding Harriet Vaughan's death.
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1799 March 2; 12 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Sarah Manning, 1799 March 3; 3 p.; Collins, John
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1799 March 9; 3 p.; Collins, John
  - ALS to Vaughan, Sarah Manning, 1799 March 9; 3 p.; Collins, John
  - ALS to Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839, 1799 March 12; 2 p.; Vaughan, Samuel, Sr., 1720-1802; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
    Regarding a family account.
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1799 March 13; 2 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Sarah Manning, 1799 March 16; 2 p.; Collins, Harriet
  - ALS to Mr. Gillet, 1799 March 18; 4 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, Samuel, 1762-, 1799 March 20; 3 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - Als to Col. Howard, Gen. Henry Dearbor, and Hallowell, Robert, 1799 March 21; 3 p.; Vaughan, Samuel, Sr., 1720-1802
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835 and Merrick, John, 1799 March 21; 3 p.; Vaughan, Samuel, Sr., 1720-1802
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1799 March 22; 1 p.; Vaughan, Sarah Hallowell
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1799 March 22; 1 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1799 March 23; 1 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1799 March 29; 3 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1799 April 2; 3 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to "my Creditors", 1799 April 2; 2 p.; Vaughan, John, 1756-1841
  - ALS to Vaughan, Samuel, 1762-, 1799 April 2; 4 p.; Vaughan, Samuel, Sr., 1720-1802
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1799 April 2; 4 p.; Vaughan, Sarah Hallowell
  - Statement of his finances to his creditors, 1799 April 3; Vaughan, John, 1756-1841
  - Als to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1799 April 5; 2 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - Als to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, [1799?] [April 7]; 3 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - Als to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1799 April 8; 3 p.; Vaughan, John, 1756-1841
  - Als to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1799 April 25; 2 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
    Regarding family property.
  - Als to Vaughan, Sarah Manning, 1799 April 27; 2 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1799 April 27; 6 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1799 May 3; 1 p.; Vaughan, John, 1756-1841
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, [1799] May 9; 2 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1799 May 15; 2 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1799 May 20; 3 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1799 May 25; 2 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1799 May 25; 1 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1799 June 12; 3 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1799 June 12; 3 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
    Regarding the family estate.
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1799 June 23; 2 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1799 June 25; 1 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - Als to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1799 June 28; 2 p.; Vaughan, Sarah Hallowell
  - Als to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1799 July 9; 2 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, John, 1756-1841, 1799 July 17; 3 p.; Vaughan, Samuel, 1762-1827
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1799 August 15; 1 p.; Vaughan, John, 1756-1841
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1799 July 22; 1 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1799 August 8; 4 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1799 August 17; 1 p.; Vaughan, John, 1756-1841
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1799 August 22; 2 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1799 August 23; 3 p.; Vaughan, John, 1756-1841
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1799 August 29; 2 p.; Vaughan, John, 1756-1841
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1799 August 31; 3 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1799 September 5; 3 p.; Collins, John
  - ALS to Vaughan, Sarah Manning, 1799 September 9; 4 p.; Vaughan, Sarah Hallowell
  - ALS to Vaughan, Samuel, 1762-, 1799 September 10; 1 p.; Stewart, James
  - ALS to Stewart, James, 1799 September 18; 3 p.; Vaughan, Samuel, 1762-1827
  - ALS to Vaughan, Samuel, 1762-, 1799 September 19; 1 p.; Stewart, James
  - ALS to Stewart, James, 1799 October 8; 2 p.; Vaughan, Samuel, 1762-1827
  - ALS to Vaughan, Samuel, 1762-, 1799 October 11; 2 p.; Stewart, James
  - ALS to Rush, Benjamin, 1746-1813, 1799 September 14; 4 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1799 September 23; 1 p.; Collins, John
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1799 September 26; 3 p.; Collins, John
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1799 October 4; 1 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1799 October 4; 4 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1799 October 8; 3 p.; Vaughan, John, 1756-1841
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1799 October 9; 2 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1799 October 12; 3 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to [Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835], 1799 October 12; 1 p.; West, Peter
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1799 October 19; 2 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1799 October 21; 1 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1799 October 30; 2 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1799 November 8; 1 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1799 November 9; 2 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1799 November 16; 3 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1799 November 20; 1 p.; Vaughan, John, 1756-1841
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1799 November 26; 4 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1799 November 29; 3 p.; Vaughan, Charles, 1759-1839
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1799 November 30; 2 p.; Vaughan, John, 1756-1841